let questions=[


    {
        numb:1,
        question:" ROLLBACK WORK asks SQL to empty the log file:",
        answer:" A. True",
        options:[
        "A. True",
        "B. False"    
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:2,
        question:" A function returns one value and has only output parameters:",
        answer:" B. False",
        options:[
        "A. True",
        "B. False"    
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:3,
        question:" Which of the following is not a valid SQL type?",
        answer:" C. DECIMAL",
        options:[
        "A. FLOAT",
        "B. NUMERIC",
        "C. DECIMAL",
        "D. CHARACTER"    
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:4,
        question:" Which datatype can store unstructured data in a column?",
        answer:" B. RAW",
        options:[
        "A. CHAR",
        "B. RAW",
        "C. NUMERIC",
        "D. VARCHAR"    
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:5,
        question:" If we have not specified ASC or DESC after a SQL ORDER BY clause,the following is used by default?",
        answer:" B. ASC",
        options:[
        "A. DESC",
        "B. ASC",
        "C. There is no default value",
        "D. None of the above"    
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:6,
        question:" ___clause creates temporary relation for the query on which it is defined?",
        answer:" A. WITH",
        options:[
        "A. WITH",
        "B. FROM",
        "C. WHERE",
        "D. SELECT"    
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:7,
        question:" A CASE SQL statements is __?",
        answer:" B. A way to establish an IF-THEN-ELSE in SQL",
        options:[
        "A. A way to establish a loop in SQL",
        "B. A way to establish an IF-THEN-ELSE in SQL",
        "C. A way to establish a data definition in SQL",
        "D. All the above"    
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:8,
        question:"__ is NOT a type of constraint in SQL language?",
        answer:" D. ALTERNATE KEY",
        options:[
         "A. FOREIGN KEY",
         "B. PRIMARY KEY",
         "C. UNIQUE",
         "D. ALTERNATE KEY"   
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:9,
        question:" Evaluate the SQL statement: SELECT ROUND(TRUNCATE (MOD(1600,10),-1),2) What will be displayed?",
        answer:" A. 0",
        options:[
        "A. 0",
        "B. 1",
        "C. 00",
        "D. An error statement"    
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb:10,
        question:" Which of the following operator can be used with a multiple-row subquery?",
        answer:" C. NOT IN",
        options:[
        "A. =",
        "B. BETWEEN",
        "C. NOT IN",
        "D. <>"    
        ]
    },

];